joby.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

### Our customers matter to us, and so does their privacy.

Your privacy is as important to us as it is to you. We respect the privacy of our visitors to our website. This online privacy statement specifies what information is collected online, the use and disclosure of your personal information you submit through our website and how it is used. 

**What Personal Information is Collected?**

In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. The information we learn from customers, however, helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at joby.com. Personal information includes your name, address, email address, phone number and any other non-public information.

**Consent**

By submitting personal information through our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your personal information according to this Privacy Policy.

**Information You Give Us**

DayMen Canada Acquisition ULC and its third party service providers receive and store personal information about you when you subscribe to a service, register to receive brochures, or participate in contests, sweepstakes and/or promotions. This information may include your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address and credit card information. You may choose not to provide such information.

**How is Information Used?**

Emails: If you provide the joby.com website with your e–mail address, you may receive e–mails from the joby.com. If you do not want to receive marketing or promotional e–mails from our website, you can unsubscribe at any time. 

If you provide feedback on any of our products and services to us, or comment in a forum, we may use such feedback and comments for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your personal information.

Sharing with Other Companies: Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share personal information with third parties and we will not disclose financial information.

We do share information with organizations that provide support services to us directly. We carefully select our Third Party Service Providers such as vendors, business partners and other organizations (such as printers, mailing houses, web hosts, order fulfillment, shipping, customer service, data management and promotional services) or that help us market our products and services. We provide these companies with the information as needed for them to perform their functions. 

**Security**

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

The joby.com web site may include links to other web sites that are not under our control. These other web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting those websites. 

A link to an outside site does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents.

**Policy Changes**

This policy is subject to change. If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our website.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or anything else, we encourage you to contact us.
